Narrator: 3
Speaker: a chemist’s
Narrator: 9
Speaker: a church
Narrator: 4
Speaker: a department store
Narrator: 6
Speaker: a hospital
Narrator: 5
Speaker: a market
Narrator: 2
Speaker: a park
Narrator: 11
Speaker: a police station
Narrator: 8
Speaker: a post office
Narrator: 10
Speaker: a shopping centre
Narrator: 7
Speaker: a supermarket
Narrator: 1
Speaker: a town hall
Narrator: 15
Speaker: an art gallery
Narrator: 16
Speaker: a castle
Narrator: 14
Speaker: a museum
Narrator: 12
Speaker: a theatre
Narrator: 13
Speaker: a zoo
Narrator: 20
Speaker: a bridge
Narrator: 19
Speaker: a river
Narrator: 18
Speaker: a road
Narrator: 21
Speaker: a square
Narrator: 17
Speaker: a street
Narrator: 23
Speaker: a bus station
Narrator: 24
Speaker: a car park
Narrator: 22
Speaker: a railway station